imonetizeit.com 2019-02-16

# Privacy Policy - iMonetizeIt

#### Last updated: May 25, 2018

We at Webtraffic LLC have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our dedication to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to personal information collected from the visitors of www.imonetizeit.com (hereafter referred to as the “Site”) as well as registered affiliates (collectively referred to as "you"). The Site operates the iMonetizeIt Affiliate Program (hereafter referred to as the “Program”) and is solely restricted to adults who are capable of entering into contractual relationships. Any person under the age of eighteen is strictly prohibited from using the Site or signing up for an account with the Program. We do not intentionally collect information on individuals under the age of eighteen. By visiting the Site, you agree and consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time, as well as the Terms of Use also located on the Site. By signing up for an affiliate account you also agree and consent to the terms of the Affiliate Terms and Conditions.

### What Information is Collected:

#### 1\. Personal Information

We collect personal information that is voluntarily provided to us for the Program via the registration form. This information may include, but is not limited to, the affiliate name, physical address, phone number, e-mail address, instant messenger address, payment method information (such as bank account information), password, and, on occasion, a unique identifier (such as mother's maiden name, for example). If an affiliate sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database.

#### 2\. Non-Personal Information and Cookies

Certain non-personal information may be collected from visitors to this Site including, but not limited to, their browser type, browser language, operating system, IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the Site. Other non-personal information may be collected such as browsing behavior, date and time of visit, the pages visited, the time spent viewing the Site, the number of times the visitor returns to the Site and click- stream data. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our Site. We may use cookies to collect this information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Site. You are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Site.

#### 3\. Use of Information

We collect personal information so that we may custom tailor the web experience for each affiliate and offer the best products and services to meet the needs of each affiliate.

We may use information collected from visitors to our Site for any of the following purposes: 

  * to send affiliates information and promotional materials about our company, which will not continue if opted out,
  * to send affiliates limited and only occasional information and promotional materials from our marketing partners and third parties,
  * to deliver highly targeted but very limited display advertisements and offers by email, which will not continue if opted out,
  * to contact affiliates to our Site when necessary,
  * to allow one-click purchases or access to proprietary content by pre-populating fields, within registration or other transaction screens, with a visitor's name, billing address, all as provided by that visitor,
  * to help diagnose problems with our server,
  * to administer our Site,
  * to conduct internal reviews of our Site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the Site),
  * to help us better understand visitors' use of our Site, and
  * to protect the security or integrity of our Site.

Since part of the personal information that is collected and safeguarded by us is your email address, we try very hard to respect your time and privacy by controlling and limiting the frequency of mailings. If you receive a mailing from us or one of our marketing partners, it is because your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future, or you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. Your registration for our affiliate program is your consent to these occasional mailing.

There may be occasions when you will be presented with special offers either from us or from third-party service or content providers, which may include communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers"). Your consent to this Privacy Policy acts as your consent to receive these occasional mailings by us and by our third-party service or content providers.

The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that an affiliate may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites. Whenever applicable, each affiliate should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site or in an email.

If you have received unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [support@imonetizeit.com](mailto:support@imonetizeit.com)

We take the complaints about unwanted e-mail very seriously and maintain an opt-out system to assist you in removing your name from our mailing list.

#### 4\. Accessing and Correcting Your Information. GDPR.

At any time through the web interface provided as part of the Services or via contact us page you have the right:

  * to access your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the rectification of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the erasure of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request to restrict processing of your personal information;
  * to object to processing of your personal information by us;
  * to request to transfer your personal information that we hold (e.g. data portability);
  * to file a complaint to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction; and
  * to withdraw any consent related to your personal information given by you.

We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

We will process your requests to us within 30 days. We will also notify a relevant supervisory authority within 72 hours from a breach related to your personal information that we hold.

We have assigned a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who may be reached via [dpo@imonetizeit.com](mailto:dpo@imonetizeit.com). Our DPO is tasked with ensuring that we acknowledge and abide by our data protection responsibilities.

We will not store personal information for more than 6 months from the date of your last active session on the Site or for more than 6 months from the date of termination of an agreement between us (whichever is earlier).

#### 5\. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@imonetizeit.com](mailto:support@imonetizeit.com)

#### 6\. Security

The Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. For all other information, visitors and affiliates should consider this communication and information to be non-confidential, and consequently, we assume no responsibility or liability if any information relating to any visitor or subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

#### 7\. Children Under the Age of 18

Our Site is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/by any possible means, make any purchases through the Website (if any), use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at [support@imonetizeit.com](mailto:support@imonetizeit.com)

#### 8\. Acceptance of these Terms

By visiting or registering to become an affiliate, you agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may at any time revise or amend any of these terms and conditions without notice. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies which may collect personal information as a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the Site.

#### 9\. Translation

In case of any discrepancy within the meanings between English and other translated versions of this Agreement, the English version of this Agreement shall prevail.

#### 10\. Contact Information

Should you have any questions – please do not hesitate to contact us at [support@imonetizeit.com](mailto:support@imonetizeit.com)
